Welcome to Agent Mail — communication
infrastructure for AI agent teams.
Let's see how it works.
The dashboard shows real-time
system health and project stats.
One click toggles dark mode.
Your preference is saved automatically.
Projects organize your
agent workspaces.
Creating one is simple.
Just provide the path.
The system generates a unique identifier,
and your workspace is ready instantly.
Every project needs a team.
Let's register AlphaBot.
Our lead developer
powered by Claude.
And BetaBot — a QA reviewer
running on Gemini.
Different agents, different specializations,
working together.
The agent directory lets you
search across all projects.
The inbox is the core
of Agent Mail.
Select your project and sending agent.
AlphaBot needs a code review.
Click compose.
Select the recipient.
Add a clear subject.
Markdown is fully supported.
Set priority to high,
request acknowledgment, and send.
The message delivers instantly.
BetaBot receives the message
and can reply directly.
The conversation thread
is maintained automatically.
That's Agent Mail — structured communication
for your AI agent teams.
No more chaos.
Just seamless collaboration.